oh yeah oh hello I was also post on
discord just to tell people that you're
alive
late it's 9:00 a.m. not late night I
know we live man it's late here
hello Russian yo yo yo you're go no no
we're flashing we've been here all
weekend well no these guys have a
slacker I went out and party today but
uh we're preparing you are your comma
tubes
these are the ones that flash good and
those are the ones that flash bet and
those are the ones we haven't flashed
yet oh yeah yeah there's a lot more well
we'll go look at the more in a minute
yeah but you know we're yeah no leaks on
any of this stuff this is this is what's
provisioning all your karma twos they
show up as comatose in the database yes
all good look we have provisioning
castes is really nice Robert some really
nice provisioning tests we want to make
sure that none of these have bugs for
you guys you know oh look we're doing
power breakdowns so yeah you know
oh yeah the the desert white edition is
that only can we show the doesn't read
edition that's never gonna sell them
we're never gonna ship them desert white
Oh this was the internal prototype you
know how Apple never shows you the
internal prototype no you got you get
black comet ooze yeah no no this is too
disgusting desert white yeah yeah we're
gonna clean all these comma tubes off
we're gonna put them in some boxes for
you guys as soon as they're done and
they pass all of our tests I can't
believe I'm drinking this Buble we
ran out of spin draft
all right look at this we got boxes I'm
gonna put them in these boxes
just good boxes we got foams over here
tons of foams for comma twos that's the
back seat yes
oh wait oh yeah I forgot about all these
comma twos yeah we get we get all these
common tools over here yeah we got
common powers here all the phones
oh yeah we're making a lot of comma twos
guys yeah we're making a lot of comet is
these are these are just boxes full of
unprocessed phones yeah this is weird
they want to know where the harnesses
are oh yeah beautiful
we got enough powers too
we got we got shipping 300 comment who's
on Monday is gonna be is gonna be crazy
should should we tell them that if they
still buy one they can still if you buy
one you can still get another 300 but
just barely just barely you can still
get in but we've sold almost 300 of
these oh you might get a hoodie oh yeah
yeah yeah we're the authors those the
hoodies that we're giving away yeah yeah
check them out just not what's inside
the car just to welcome to the fleet
yeah yeah Oh get off in our discord yeah
do we ship the hoodies to India we ship
the hoodies worldwide DHL goes will ship
them wait we don't ship to Russia
anymore oh wow no do we have like a we
don't ship to Iran I'm sorry it's
illegal for us we'd love to we don't
want to reject our any in business but I
don't think we're allowed to I think
there's sanctions but will absolutely
ship to India , two's yo you know what's
in those boxes over there more comma
powers and harnesses 3000 we test all
the phones
how long to prep a comma to write now
way too long right now it takes so long
we're practically losing money on them
now that's a lie but you know it takes
longer than I'd like we're spending more
money than I'd like they're really nice
though I hope I've been I've been I've
been talent I've been saying over and
over this week I'm like we got to make
these ones really beautiful because I
know that you guys who bought them are
gonna uh they're gonna go tell your
friends about how beautiful it is and
they're gonna buy more and that's gonna
continue the cycle Oh
should I should I show you we'll take a
quick look at it we'll take a quick look
at it for a minute it's unreal yo it's
unreal that's this month well not this
month it's a little bit more than this
month but uh yeah so a lot of these
things comes a suit well we are
profitable for the month of January and
you guys are gonna have fun
whoo to catch this video live you guys
are gonna have fun check it and uh check
in the replays for this
yeah test them out in Seoul over here
you know I know you guys all can't wait
to install that dash cam saw her oh yeah
yeah yeah we meet we may be a store real
fast um remember that if you're in
America would you say that prime is us
only right I could if you're in America
you get three free months of comma Prime
with your device and that means that
you'll be able to install the software
without even having to connect to Wi-Fi
nice just a quick video that's pretty
much all I wanted to show you I don't
really have 34 this late it's late it's
really late
yeah now we can have coatings James
maybe maybe we can go back to coding
streams but I just wanted to show you
guys that the comma twos are real and
hopefully hopefully assuming assuming
this all works
assuming all our provisioning works I'm
sure well assuming it all works we will
be shipping them out on Monday
do you guys
yeah
that's that quick you'd apply
we're not gonna make the hardware
schematics open-source this is how karma
makes money we appreciate all your
support if you haven't bought one yet by
a comment - it is the best product on my
eyes ever made it's the EON without all
the books there's been a big spike
that's been a really big spike in Oppo
traffic lately we've got Andy's YouTube
video which which did wonders for us and
then and Hubble sphere was also in that
video
if you guys haven't checked it out its
autopilot versus open pilot self-driving
test more competitive where it were
competitive with with the best systems
car and driver also did open pilot
comparison which went out in the print
magazine yeah it's not even online yet
it's in the print magazine so if you got
a car and driver print magazine you can
check out open pilot compared to auto
pilot and super cruise definitely people
we want to be compared to um the other
piece of big news you guys read the
medium post is that ultimate Isle is not
being developed on master
we've already merged in quite a few pull
requests it's gonna be much easier to
work with everybody on developing it to
open source 1.0 hardware that's it
cuz it
bye have a good night everybody enjoy
your comet oohs when they arrive you
haven't bought one yet shop comet III
you can still just barely get in in the
first 300 just make sure to do that do
you mean well I make new hardware for
1.00 no this is the hydrophone point Oh
the Karma - is gonna run open pilot 1.0
do I plan to provide long support for
TSS P cars yeah bad if you remove the D
s here which we don't recommend because
it disables a B what can you do with it
now well it makes a great paperweight
umm you can tell people you bought one
uh what's the number at how many have we
sold almost three hundred I wanna see
you have - I - are you guys we've made
two hundred two hundred fifty four
thousand dollars in the last 30 days we
rich boys we rich um vision is fully
open the model is fully open I actually
actually I know there was a complaint
that the models are encrypted there in
DLC format which is not encryption at
all but there's actually a tensorflow
model in there right now
hey do you have the cross ball I think
we even have the cross model if you go
right now to come open pilot yeah I'm
sure we have the cross model yeah
they're in there they're just our cross
files
um it's open I mean I don't know what's
more open than that you want the date
it'll be open no no no no do we do
quantization and pruning we do
quantization for the monitoring model
also if you want to buy they may even a
hit me up we sell data where we're
sketchy like that Zuckerberg you know
someone was like someone I read it was
like they're gonna be sketchy like
Zuckerberg and sell data
yo I wish we could be sketchy like
Zuckerberg that guy's rich no I'm
kidding I wouldn't sell data if it was
for shitty people like ads but if it was
for self-driving car people
yeah then don't we sell the data so yeah
do we do our ell models hair looks
better thank you come on in grab get the
models if you just go into open pilot
models directory now they're fully open
they're cross files enjoy let me see if
I can merge oh sweet I can merge this
pull request oh I love merging pull
request is such a good feeling um isn't
the day to your main advantage no anyway
we have look put it this way this is
just real talk we have thousand daily
actives how much does it cost to hire a
thousand people to drive around remember
that kind of driving hour two hours a
day so thousand people two hours a day
let's say pay them so you pay them ten
bucks an hour
so that's 20k a day dude twenty twenty K
a day is what way mow probably spends on
janitorial services yeah let's see 7.3
million for away most janitorial budget
I could almost believe that so the data
is not you know that's that's even like
paying people ten bucks an hour you can
you can ship out stuff to people
anybody can compete on data now that's
not what our advantages our advantage is
not being delusional like a lot of
self-driving car coming how long does it
take to train the entire driving model a
long time now we don't buy data um last
24-hour activity yes someone's got to
write that wouldn't an engineer for that
hey now we're gonna go 15 minutes on the
stream any last questions in the last 20
seconds yes they were talking about sale
again I know I know
thank you all for supporting us thank
you all for buying common tools we're
very happy to have you here with us on
this journey if you haven't bought one
yet shop comma dot a good night